<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learning Sprint on Giovanni Licameli</title>
    <link>https://novabutter.github.io/tags/learning-sprint/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learning Sprint on Giovanni Licameli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://novabutter.github.io/tags/learning-sprint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: June 22-June-28</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-22-learning-sprint-june-22-june-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-22-learning-sprint-june-22-june-28/</guid>
      <description>June 22-June-28 Learning The name of the game this week is finish the tasks. I&amp;rsquo;ll be busy, but I have a new philosophy in place I plan to apply to boost my productivity and actually accomplish these topics. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what comes this week but I do intend to finish everything on the list. Here is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be up to.
My intended focuses:
 Start Unreal Engine Learning Windows Exploit Development Course Review Post  Repeating Activities include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: June 15 - June 20</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-15-learning-sprint-june-15-june-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-15-learning-sprint-june-15-june-20/</guid>
      <description>June 15 - June 20 Learning This past sprint was absolutely one of my worst yet (arguably). This week will not be a bust, but a success. While the items on the calendar this week are rollover from the previous sprint entirely, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to accomplish them even while being out of town. These are pretty realistic goals with a minor exception. This is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be up to this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 25 - May 31</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-25-learning-sprint-may-25-may-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-25-learning-sprint-may-25-may-31/</guid>
      <description>May 25 - May 31 Learning For the previous week I get extremely side-tracked with a few specific projects. As they were not related to my progress in shifting my actual progress and more relating to personal interest. And that issue cannot seep into this week. Thankfully that is simply not a luxury I can afford anymore; too much more of a slip and I&amp;rsquo;ll be significantly off schedule. While schedule isn&amp;rsquo;t everything and I am human, I truly am going to try to stick to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 18 - May 24</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-18-learning-sprint-may-18-may-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-18-learning-sprint-may-18-may-24/</guid>
      <description>May 18 - May 24 Learning Last week I did pretty well with what I learned, but this week I have a serious amount of ambition. I need a job. Soon. And as of right now I have had very little success finding employers who will take my skills. To change that, I am doing an additional course this week to increase my marketability now that I have an idea of some of the requirements of a security expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 13 - May 17</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-13-learning-sprint-may-13-may-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-13-learning-sprint-may-13-may-17/</guid>
      <description>May 13 - May 17 Learning As always, this is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 4 - May 10</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-4-learning-sprint-may-4-may-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-4-learning-sprint-may-4-may-10/</guid>
      <description>May 4 - May 10 Learning Sprint As always, this is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Apr. 20 - Apr. 26</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-20-learning-sprint-april-20-april-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-20-learning-sprint-april-20-april-26/</guid>
      <description>Apr. 20 - Apr. 26 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Apr. 14 - Apr. 19</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-14-learning-sprint-april-14-april-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-14-learning-sprint-april-14-april-19/</guid>
      <description>Apr. 14 - Apr. 19 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Mar. 30 - Apr. 5</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-30-learning-sprint-mar-30-apr-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-30-learning-sprint-mar-30-apr-5/</guid>
      <description>Mar. 30 - Apr. 5 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Mar. 23 - Mar. 29</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-23-learning-sprint-mar-23-mar-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-23-learning-sprint-mar-23-mar-29/</guid>
      <description>Mar. 23 - Mar. 29 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Feb. 10 - Feb. 16</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-11-learning-sprint-feb-10-feb-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-11-learning-sprint-feb-10-feb-16/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 10 - Feb 16 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. For a larger outlook on what I am doing to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.
Last week I prioritized my tasks and started/finished what needed to be done. However the completion level of said tasks was rather low. This was all the fault of my own, but nonetheless I&amp;rsquo;m proud of my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Feb. 3 - Feb. 9</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-2-learning-sprint-feb-3-feb-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-2-learning-sprint-feb-3-feb-9/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 3 - Feb 9 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. For a larger outlook on what I am doing to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.
Last week I learned plenty, but only a few items. My time was well invested but poorly planned. I spent hours upon hours dedicating myself to a task&amp;rsquo;s completion. While this completed the bigger tasks I suffered on total task completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Jan. 27 - Feb. 2</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-1-29-learning-sprint-jan-27-feb-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-1-29-learning-sprint-jan-27-feb-2/</guid>
      <description>Jan. 27 - Feb. 2 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>