<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Update on Giovanni Licameli</title>
    <link>https://novabutter.github.io/tags/update/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Update on Giovanni Licameli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://novabutter.github.io/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: June 22-June-28</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-22-learning-sprint-june-22-june-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-22-learning-sprint-june-22-june-28/</guid>
      <description>June 22-June-28 Learning The name of the game this week is finish the tasks. I&amp;rsquo;ll be busy, but I have a new philosophy in place I plan to apply to boost my productivity and actually accomplish these topics. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what comes this week but I do intend to finish everything on the list. Here is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be up to.
My intended focuses:
 Start Unreal Engine Learning Windows Exploit Development Course Review Post  Repeating Activities include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: June 15 - June 20</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-21-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-21-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>June 15 - June 20 Learning Review While I was working this week I did not accomplish what I had hoped to. I didn&amp;rsquo;t work as much as I had anticipated for a few reasons but they are not important; I still failed to accomplish a majority of these tasks.
My intended focuses:
 Update Passwords Start Unreal Engine Learning Windows Exploit Development Course Review Post  Repeating Activities include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: June 15 - June 20</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-15-learning-sprint-june-15-june-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-15-learning-sprint-june-15-june-20/</guid>
      <description>June 15 - June 20 Learning This past sprint was absolutely one of my worst yet (arguably). This week will not be a bust, but a success. While the items on the calendar this week are rollover from the previous sprint entirely, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to accomplish them even while being out of town. These are pretty realistic goals with a minor exception. This is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be up to this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: May 25th - June 14th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-14-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-14-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>May 25th - June 14th Learning Review It&amp;rsquo;s been a longer sprint than intended, and I really did a poor job at accomplishing the tasks I had given myself in the past few weeks but nearly for justifiable reasons. Regardless, there absolutely was little productivity in accomplishing the intended tasks. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I was able to get done versus what I had intended:
My intended focuses:
 Complete OverTheWire Bandit CTF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 25 - May 31</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-25-learning-sprint-may-25-may-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-25-learning-sprint-may-25-may-31/</guid>
      <description>May 25 - May 31 Learning For the previous week I get extremely side-tracked with a few specific projects. As they were not related to my progress in shifting my actual progress and more relating to personal interest. And that issue cannot seep into this week. Thankfully that is simply not a luxury I can afford anymore; too much more of a slip and I&amp;rsquo;ll be significantly off schedule. While schedule isn&amp;rsquo;t everything and I am human, I truly am going to try to stick to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: May 18th - May 24th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-24-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-24-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>May 18th - May 24th Learning Review This past week while I was productive, I did get caught up in a particular activity that completely slowed my progress. I am not completely satisfied with my task accomplishments and am now behind schedule but I may have a slight opportunity to catch up. It&amp;rsquo;ll be a bit tough but not impossible.
My intended focuses:
 Complete OverTheWire Bandit CTF. Update Passwords Start Unreal Engine Learning Finish Up Final Work for the Cyber Range  Repeating Activities include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 18 - May 24</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-18-learning-sprint-may-18-may-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-18-learning-sprint-may-18-may-24/</guid>
      <description>May 18 - May 24 Learning Last week I did pretty well with what I learned, but this week I have a serious amount of ambition. I need a job. Soon. And as of right now I have had very little success finding employers who will take my skills. To change that, I am doing an additional course this week to increase my marketability now that I have an idea of some of the requirements of a security expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: May 13th- May 17th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-17-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-17-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>May 13th- May 17th Learning Review This past week I did pretty well with my productivity. I had just finished finals and started my sprint really on Wednesday, so I had about 5 days. For that time I was decently productive and effectively accomplished many of my tasks. My focus was pretty unhindered minus me falling slightly ill tonight toward the end and I am proud of what I accomplished. Here were my focuses and what I got done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 13 - May 17</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-13-learning-sprint-may-13-may-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-13-learning-sprint-may-13-may-17/</guid>
      <description>May 13 - May 17 Learning As always, this is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: May 4th - May 10th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-12-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-12-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>May 4 - May 10 Learning Review Over the past week I was absolutely slammed with last minute work for my school projects as I approach graduation. Most of it was long essays that just took time and weren&amp;rsquo;t of any relating value. Some of them my professors assigned out of nowhere and they were due within less than 24 hours because they still had content to cover. Due to this fact (and a few more that are not school realted), I did not accomplish as much as I had hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: May 4 - May 10</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-4-learning-sprint-may-4-may-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-4-learning-sprint-may-4-may-10/</guid>
      <description>May 4 - May 10 Learning Sprint As always, this is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: Apr. 20th - May 3rd</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-3-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-5-3-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>Apr. 20 - May 3 Learning Review This past few weeks (I missed the preview week review and post) I learned a small amount. I did accomplish a few things on my list, though not nearly as many as I had previously wanted. Most of my items were disappointingly long, but I did follow my time-constraint suggestions to the best of my ability which when I was working did help. Here is what I did over the past 2 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Apr. 20 - Apr. 26</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-20-learning-sprint-april-20-april-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-20-learning-sprint-april-20-april-26/</guid>
      <description>Apr. 20 - Apr. 26 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: Apr. 14th - Apr. 19th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-19-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-19-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>Apr. 14 - Apr. 19 Learning Review I did a fantastic amount of learning this week and was able to if not complete, work on nearly every single item I had intended to complete. I was able to learn some basics about Splunk, finish multiple Linux Basics series I have had stocked for a while, do some reading on articles and work on the courses I have been doing in parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Apr. 14 - Apr. 19</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-14-learning-sprint-april-14-april-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-14-learning-sprint-april-14-april-19/</guid>
      <description>Apr. 14 - Apr. 19 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: Mar. 30th - Apr. 12th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-13-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-4-13-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>Mar. 30 - April 12 Learning Review Minus skipping a week, I did not get as much done as I had hoped. I got distracted with a few games, some actual awesome productivity, and homework. Despite this, I did finish a few things, which lately has been rather rare.
My intended focuses:
 Complete OverTheWire Bandit CTF. Light Splunk Learning Finish a YouTube Series on Linux Administration Start the Metasploit Unleashed course/book Finish SMTP &amp;amp; IMAP Lab Finish work on Cyber Range backup deployment server (for work)  Repeating Activities include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Mar. 30 - Apr. 5</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-30-learning-sprint-mar-30-apr-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-30-learning-sprint-mar-30-apr-5/</guid>
      <description>Mar. 30 - Apr. 5 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: Mar. 23rd - Mar. 29th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-30-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-30-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>Mar. 23 - 29 Learning Review Last week I was moving around a lot from school to home. I got very little done in this list, but outside the list I finished plenty. I focused a lot on other work that needed to be done. Now I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to focus on these things going into next week.
My intended focuses:
 Complete OverTheWire Bandit CTF. Light Splunk Learning Finish a YouTube Series on Linux Administration Start the Metasploit Unleashed course/book Finish SMTP &amp;amp; IMAP Lab Finish work on Cyber Range backup deployment server (for work)  Repeating Activities include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Mar. 23 - Mar. 29</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-23-learning-sprint-mar-23-mar-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-3-23-learning-sprint-mar-23-mar-29/</guid>
      <description>Mar. 23 - Mar. 29 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Feb. 10 - Feb. 16</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-11-learning-sprint-feb-10-feb-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-11-learning-sprint-feb-10-feb-16/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 10 - Feb 16 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. For a larger outlook on what I am doing to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.
Last week I prioritized my tasks and started/finished what needed to be done. However the completion level of said tasks was rather low. This was all the fault of my own, but nonetheless I&amp;rsquo;m proud of my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: Feb. 3rd - Feb 9th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-11-last-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-11-last-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 3 - 9 Learning Review Last week I was actually pretty light on homework. I focused on other things outside of the scope of my Trello learning as well as inside of it. Since the CCDC competition is this upcoming week (last week it was 2 weeks away) most of my focus was on learning security for my box. Thankfully, this was on my Trello board of things to do so some of it counted, but I still failed to organize enough to get a lot of things done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Feb. 3 - Feb. 9</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-2-learning-sprint-feb-3-feb-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-2-learning-sprint-feb-3-feb-9/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 3 - Feb 9 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. For a larger outlook on what I am doing to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.
Last week I learned plenty, but only a few items. My time was well invested but poorly planned. I spent hours upon hours dedicating myself to a task&amp;rsquo;s completion. While this completed the bigger tasks I suffered on total task completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: Jan. 20th - Jan. 26th</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-2-last-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-2-2-last-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>Feb. 3 - Feb 9 Learning Review Last week I had quite a few things to do. I was a bit worried about school starting getting in the way of some of my learning, but nonetheless I was confident I could do well.
Well&amp;hellip;.I didn&amp;rsquo;t do great.
Most of the items I had planned simply never happened and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t due to lack of time. My interests were all over the place and I ended up going down multiple rabbit holes of things I wanted to learn rather than had scheduled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: Jan. 27 - Feb. 2</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-1-29-learning-sprint-jan-27-feb-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-1-29-learning-sprint-jan-27-feb-2/</guid>
      <description>Jan. 27 - Feb. 2 Learning Sprint This is a weekly learning sprint update. The purpose is to outline my goals and tasks of learning throughout the week. At the end of each weekly I will evaluate my completed and incomplete tasks hoping to identify and streamline my best working/learning habits. Additionally, those that read here can see what I’m up to and track my weekly progress. For a larger outlook on what I’m up to, check out my Trello Board which changes daily &amp;amp; is what my weeks are based off of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Sprint Review</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-1-28-sprint-review-and-blog-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-1-28-sprint-review-and-blog-move/</guid>
      <description>Moving Blog For about 4 months now I&amp;rsquo;ve been hosting my blog on wordpress to show my updates. That was absolutely fine. Tools were easy, posts had no issue. But I&amp;rsquo;ve found that increasingly individuals in the Cybersecurity world have been posting their guides and successes to github rather than to an external blog. So that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing; moving to github.
Over the next week or so I&amp;rsquo;ll be moving posts from wordpress to github, so there will be slightly more activity than usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sprint: June 29-July 5</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-29-learning-sprint-june-29-july-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-29-learning-sprint-june-29-july-5/</guid>
      <description>June 29-July 5 Learning Last week was a massive failure. While I was busy with things I found worthwhile, I did not follow the tasks at hand. If you take a look at the previous week it appears I finished nothing but behind the scenes I had a lot going on that I still cannot yet mention. What I can mention is this: I had a ton of fun with the and it was a great review since I had taken the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Review: June 22 - June 28</title>
      <link>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-28-learning-sprint-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://novabutter.github.io/blog/2020-6-28-learning-sprint-review/</guid>
      <description>June 22 - June 28 Learning Review I truly feel like a child sometimes shooting blindly at cool things I observe or look at. Then I get sidetracked but feel like I am probably doing a task worthwhile when I am in reality completely missing the target. When will I learn? Plenty of time for opportunity all squandered by who knows what? Definitely could have done more this week even though I had little distractions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>